[Music]
[Música]
Okay family let's go see Quesada and
vale familia vamos a verlo de quesada y
Mister Ego okay what a mystery well he's
lo de míster ego vale qué misterio pues
back he's shined be me the truth is I
ha vuelto ha lucido sea mi la verdad yo
these types of people well the truth is I don't
este tipo de personas pues la verdad no
think they should be on the internet from the
creo que deberían estar en la red de
heart you know that I'm not a
corazón sabéis que no tengo nada de
moralist progressive none contact this
moralista progre ninguna contacten está
but I'm that the issue of
pero yo es que el tema de las amenazas
physical threats and that or rather for people like the
físicas y esa o sea para gente como el
bull the heifer not in things like that
torete el vaquilla no en cosas así que
we saw in the movies these of seven
veíamos en las películas éstas de siete
virgins is fine but I kind of think that
vírgenes está bien pero medio creo que
in the society that we should live
ya en la sociedad que deberíamos vivir
in the times that we should live this thing
en los tiempos que deberíamos vivir esto
of threats of childbirth the face that
de las amenazas de parto la cara que me
tells me what they hit your mother
dice lo que le pegan a tu madre
because your dog hits her paw I
porque le pega una pata tu perro
understand that the new one returns it
entiendo que la nueva le devuelva
but for a loss of internet or
pero que por una pérdida de internet o
threats to someone well I don't see it the
amenazas a alguien pues no lo veo la
truth I don't see it I
verdad no lo veo
break the face of cross or the face
rompo la cara de cruz o la cara
I don't report it the day because more or
yo no lo denuncien el día porque más o
less we did that debate that more or
menos hicimos el debate ese que más o
less left the golf the party in peace and it
menos quedó las golf la fiesta en paz y
stayed there the thing is you know but I no
quedó ahí la cosa está sabe pero yo no
no
no
in the first place
en primer lugar
enters the debate the king who you don't
entra en debate the king quien tú no
know  Who you mess with, who you mess with
sabes quién te metes con quién te metes
or whatever,
o lo que sea
you don't know who messes with you, the
tú no sabes con quién te mete todo lo
best thing you can see is a very
mejor puedes ver a una persona muy
formalistic person on the internet and you don't know the
formalista en internet y tú no sabes el
past that person has, the life that
pasado que tiene esa persona la vida que
person leads, what they have lived for
lleva esa persona lo que ha vivido para
you, like you were talking about coolest canio topics, well maybe
tú como tú hablabas de temas canío más
you think you know
guay pues a lo mejor tú crees que sabes
what I'm saying, well imagine rowing,
lo que te digo pues imagínate rowing
imagine rowing, they asked me how many
imagínate rowing me preguntaron cuántas
fights, some low-level event and I don't
peleas algún evento de poca kahn y yo no
talk about that,
hablo de eso
imagine,
imagínate
no, the least I do is like what happened to me
no yo la mínima que hago es como me pasó
with the note s of the dog, no matter how many
con el nota s de lo del perro no por más
things go through my head and no matter how much
que se pasen cosas por la cabeza y por
I always do, report it
más que yo lo que hago siempre denuncia
and I'm telling you, for the sake of getting a report, they
y ya te digo yo para que te llega una
won't do it, they won't do it
denuncia no lo hacen para no lo hacen
anymore, for the sake of getting a report, you have to
más para que te llega una denuncia y
go to another city to testify, on
tienes que ir a otra ciudad a declarar
a January afternoon, a lawyer, a hobby,
la tarde de enero un abogado pasatiempo
appeal, if they condemn you, even if it's a
recurrir si te condena aunque sea una
fine, the best is 500 euros, but they
multa la mejor de 500 euros pero ya te
condemn you, you know, there are criminal records for
condenan te que hay antecedentes durante
a few months, you have to have I don't know what, well, they
unos meses tienes que tener no sé qué ya
have more, I'm telling you, I'm
pues tiene más ya te digo yo
telling you  that I don't know anymore I'll
yo ya te digo yo que ya no la sé más
tell you that then I
ya te digo yo que entonces yo prefiero
always prefer to use the law even though sometimes
siempre utilizar la ley aunque a veces
I've made mistakes but you use it it will go to the
equivoqué pero la utilizas irá a la
part that no longer uses the laws that
parte que ya no utilizar las leyes que
people regret binary that does not hit is that it does
lamenta la gente binarias que no pega es
not sting until the banquet wanted to
que no pica hasta el banquete quiso
hit the good one when those who do not hit already look
pegar la buena cuando los que no pega ya
bad you or the people who
que quedan mal tú o sea la gente que
still have in their mentality
todavía tiene en su mentalidad
that when you threaten someone this
que cuando tú amenazas a alguien este
delivery the face that you are above
parto la cara que tú quedas por encima
the other that you look good or something
del otro que tú quedas bien o algo de
true you have a very strange taste you do not
verdad tenéis un gusto muy raro no
look good when you say that I
quedáis bien cuando decís eso a mí me
like people who are
gustan las personas que quedan por
above with arguments and with knowing how to speak
encima con argumento y con saber hablar
not like threats to see who hit
no como amenaza a ver quién pegaba
hard Sherman eta and if you hit and if you kiss
fuerte sherman eta y si tu pega y si tu
me and on the street and we
me besan y por la calle y nos
meet at an event and you hit me and
encontramos en un evento y tú me pegas y
I do not know fight what does it mean that you
yo no sé pelea que quiere decir que tú
are better than me imagine you hit me
eres mejor que yo imagínate tú me pegas
and they break my face
y me rompen la cara
what happens you are better than me that's why you are
qué pasa eres mejor que yo por eso
more right you are more machine
tienes más razón eres más máquina
maguayo something
maguayo algo
hit me or
pégame o
look it's fine
mira está bien
like lions not the male the one who goes the one who is the
como los leones no el macho el que va el
most  the male roars he is the one who
que más ruge el macho es el que el que
fights the best it is not in
mejor pelea no
the jungle okay but in the city it is
son la selva vale pero ya en la ciudad
not
no vale
worth it but he did not achieve that in his day quesada justified all the empty ministries and said that he was a character but well in the end he ends up posting a tweet in the end javier and he will tell me he was right how many times do we see this tweet that is why I hate me so much on the front pages and
por eso yo en planas me odia tanto y
has the spite and the obsession that he has
tiene la inquina y la obsesión que tiene
with me
conmigo
javi he hits you but with an argument well that is what I
javi te pega pero con argumento pues eso
like to hear robin
me gusta escuchar robin
that is what I like he listens to me I
eso es lo que me gusta me escucha
hit with my tongue
yo golpeo con mi lengua
but how many times do we hear this at the
pero cuántas veces escuchamos esto al
end of the month a few by a
cabo del mes unas cuantas por unas
few and this this is what I am
cuantas y esto esto es lo que yo me
left with for
quedo
this already like what is it that he would
por esto ya en plan a que es que esto le
love for this to happen to him but it does not happen to him
encantaría que le pasara pero no le pasa
the devil knows more because he is old than because he is the
más sabe el por viejo que por
devil but there are times that there are times that there are
pero hay veces que hay veces que
older devils and you know less than
hay diablos más viejos y sabes menos que
others also I tell you
otros también os digo
well here what happens let's watch the
bueno aquí lo que pasa vamos a ver el
video that was first so that
vídeo que estaba primero para que se vea
this click can be seen and so on okay
este clic y demás vale
the villain character the voice of the people and
el personaje villano la voz del pueblo y
then when the time comes you can't
luego a la hora de la verdad no te
stand one  criticism bro
puedes bancar una crítica bro
in an insult that does not gate that is a
en un insulto que no gate que es una
criticism and deep down you know that you had
crítica y en el fondo sabes que tuviste
a bad performance guys context it got
un mal desempeño muchachos contexto se
messed up yesterday on Valentine's Day
lió ayer en el día de san valentín
relating chilling quietly with
relacionando chilling tranquilamente con
your mother the father is here or has
vuestra madre el padre está aquí o se ha
Paulet gone here you have gone
paulet aquí os ha ido
Pauli you are going to yell at the ladies
pauli tú vas a gritarle a las señoras el
tomorrow's video
vídeo de mañana
answer me for the clash I want
contéstame por el choque quiero que la
people to be aware
gente tenga constancia
but you know the lady's topics
pero tú conoces los temas de la señora
if she wants she tells me
si quiere me dice
but you go on about the lady's topics
pero tú vamos en los temas de la señora
like when she's talking about
en plan para cuando está hablando de
someone you put someone's photos
alguien tú pones las fotos de alguien
for tomorrow at 7 the videos of each
para mañana a las 7 los vídeos de cada
main one are at 7
principal son a las 7
at 7 in the afternoon Spain if they talk about you
a 7 de la tarde españa si hablan de ti
if I'm not reading the sentence
si no estoy leyendo la sentencia
Antonella well the video
antonella bien el vídeo
you are going to see put click when I
tú vas a ver poner click de cuando yo
mentioned something
mencioné cosa
and I get in the middle
y me me por medio
or I don't know what time it is
o no sé qué hora es
the truth is that a great evening and a
la verdad que una gran velada y un
moment in
momento de
May I need editors like for example
mayo necesito editores como por ejemplo
the clash the devices
del choque los device
I need editors dude that
yo necesito editores tío que
follow the content and that I don't have to
sigan el contenido y que yo no tenga que
be here what I mentioned take here you
estar aquí esto que mencionó toma aquí
have the click here no  but people
tienes el clic aquí no sino que gente
who follow the content and know the
que sigue el contenido y que se sepan
animes
los animes
they are the days support me I will say today the
ellos son los días me apoyen diré hoy el
main video of all the topics that
vídeo principal de todos los temas que
they talk about live today the main video is
hablan en directo hoy el vídeo principal
going to be this one this one from Joan Plana
va a ser este este el de joan plana
and he alone takes the video and knows what clip to
y él solo coja el vídeo y sepa qué clip
put in and put things from a year ago this made
meter y meter cosas de hace un año este
a year ago there
hecho hace un año
is
ay
an editor who knows the
un editor que conozca a la perfección el
content perfectly and the animes in our days you
contenido y los anime en nuestros días
know what I'm telling you but let it be known the
sabes lo que te digo pero que se sepa la
gentleman hurt the kids who
señor hería a la chavalería que se
observe everything
observa todo
imagine you take the video and in Plana and you
imagínate coges el vídeo y en plana y tú
put something from Jean Nouvel you
le metes una cosa del jean nouvel le
put something else that we skip in another
metes otra cosa que saltamos en otro
live from Great Plana he puts it in when there is
directo de gran plana le mete cuando
a plan to God I don't know what and to
haya un plan a dio no sé qué y se para
edit the video pim pim pim pim without
montar el vídeo pim pim pim pim sin que
me having to be this that he mentioned
yo tenga que estar esto que mencionó
is in a live from seven years ago
está en un directo de hace siete años
everything I say he said it and wow in a video I don't
todo yo digo lo dijo y vaya en un vídeo
know what you know
no sé qué sabe
that would be ideal
eso sería ideal
from the night of the scene that they
de la noche de la escena que no me
kept coming to me he sent a photo of
paraban de llegar ha enviado una foto
mine of a photo of mine a photo on
mía de una foto mía una foto en
instagram media
instagram media los
passes them  and of course I see this I
pasa y claro me veo esto
see this there are no ways to generate
me veo esto no existen formas de generar
toxicity says mister some of us can
toxicidad dice mister algunos podemos
say without being rappers and have proof of
decir sin ser raperos y tener pruebas de
being so others have to say they are
serlo otros tienen que decir ser
journalists and they don't even have that
periodistas y no tienen ni la eso
difference the next one he uploads and
diferencias la siguiente que suba el y
if I don't lower his face [ __ ] he raps
si no le bajo la cara ostias que rapea
better
mejor
than said gold autumn I study what I
de otoño que dicho oro yo estudio que he
said bro I hate the
dicho hermano me cagan los muertos del
mister's dead or something I said bros I say
míster o algo que he dicho bros digo
bro what have I put I
hermano que le he puesto yo
say more he lowered his face or rather the
digo más le bajó la cara o sea que el
rapper is
rapero
very pissed off
mucho pinilla
the character
el personaje
forgive
perdona
my god if the mister is acting
madre mía si el míster se está poniendo
like this what is disrespectful to him a lot
así lo que se le falta al respeto pila
bro having made a [ __ ] personal attack
hermano haber hecho un ataque personal
go to the video and I'm going to
de la entra al vídeo y los voy a
see them Hawaii because there are ways to
ver hawai porque existen formas de
generate toxicity a man Hawaii because
generar toxicidad un man hawai porque
then notice that in the mystery gut
luego fíjate que en el misterio tripa
that has been a soporific battery the
que ha sido una batería soporífera la
most disappointing battery of the day
batería más decepcionante de la jornada
but by far they are neither good mister
pero de lejos ya no están ni bien míster
ego nor has it been good you it's that on top
ego ni ha estado bien ti es que encima
of going to lose alone it's not that I was
de ir para pierde solo no es que me
interested he gains turban it's that time he
interesó gana turbana es que tiempo
lost only financing and one and it's that
perdió sólo financiación y una y es que
I am then neither in the end they are going to
me esté luego tampoco al final se van a
the replica because they were fighting to
la réplica porque estaban luchando por
see who did worse, I really do
ver quién lo hacía peor verdaderamente
n't know why he was super
no sé por qué tiró a estar súper
unfocused, he doesn't concentrate at any
descentrado no se concentra en ningún
time, the battle is not that he didn't
momento la batalla no es que no nos nos
score a point on us literally the type of
metió un punto literalmente el tipo
forgettable mystery not soporific
misterio olvidable no soporífero
of all the fm is that we have to
de todas las fm es es que llevamos a día
this day 2022 of these new seasons I
de hoy 2022 de estas nuevas temporadas
think without a doubt in the worst
creo que sin lugar a dudas en la peor
battle that we have in the calendar I
batalla que llevamos en el calendario
leave you complete so you can see that there
les dejo completo para que veáis que no
are no self-cuts that there is no lack of
hay autos cortes que no hay falta de
respect that there are no insults or the way
respeto que no hay insultos ni la forma
in which what I am saying that for me is
en lo que estoy diciendo que para mí es
the worst is going to have what goes of the year
la peor va a tener lo que va de año
form
forma
the way
la forma
people are telling him in the chat
la gente le está diciendo en el chat
the way and it's like the way
la forma y es como la forma
the faith the way of the other's turn who has
la fe la forma del turno del otro que ha
said that he lowers his face to another not
dicho que le baja la cara a otra no
the ways
las formas
but what way then he has a bad
pero qué forma luego tiene una mala
battle for a pelotari soporific
batalla para un pelotari soporífera
forgettable mystery is now for other
olvidable misterio ya está para otras
things truly
cosas verdaderamente
compete and have a day I explained
competir y tener un día explicó
that the threat that I put to my mystery is
que la amenaza que me puse a mi misterio
worth if they catch you directly they are
vale si te cogen directo están
telling your mouse army and two to
diciéndole a tu ejército de ratón y dos
come and give me irrefutable evidence
que vengan a darme pruebas irrefutables
and if we go to Seville you still have to
y si vamos a sevilla aún te tiene que
put on the face of another
poner la cara de otro
good one,
bueno
wow, the day,
vaya el día
host, gave air, we show it now, no, we don't
dio aire lo enseñamos ya no no
show the new icon that I love
enseñamos el icono nuevo que me encanta
but it is that I love it
pero es que me encanta
if we show it, air
si lo enseñamos aire
we are going to release the new designs right now, I am
vamos a sacar los nuevos diseños ya
going to release them on FT, it does
voy a sacar en ft
not affect him in the future because he had
no le afecte de cara al futuro porque
a bad day it will be, I do not know if it
haya tenido un mal día va a ser no sé si
is conditioned because seeing his
está condicionada porque ver a sus
colleagues their sorrows and such, well,
colegas sus penas y tal pues la
discouraged, he had a bad day because we
desanimado tenía mal día por que estamos
are talking about a professional criticism, each one is something personal that can happen in the end they are people and they are conditioned by feelings, situations, contexts and July about the battle, it has really been very frankly forgettable, soporific and the grace came at the end when precisely not precisely McCann, look, they are a professional criticism also
fíjate son una crítica profesional also
Mr. ego's response
la contestación de míster ego
is first to make a personal attack on me
es primero hacerme un ataque personal
because he cannot counter the
porque no puede contra argumentar el
argument that you have done a poor performance
argumento de has hecho un mal desempeño
on FM, truly win the battle
en fm s verdaderamente ganar la batalla
because to throw for this fatal directly
porque tir para esta fatal directamente
what you are going to do is I am a rapper and the
lo que tú vas es al yo soy rapero y la
difference is that you say the journalist
diferencia es que tú dices el periodista
and he does not even have that, you  who claims to be so
y no tiene ni la eso tú que dice ser tan
street brother, coming from the bottom
de calle hermano de venir de abajo
should be proud of a kid
debería de estar orgulloso de un chaval
like me who without resources or means and without
como yo que sin recursos ni medios y sin
studies since the age of 16 can live
estudios desde los 16 años puede vivir
off what he likes, off a dream that he
de lo que le gusta de un sueño que
has always pursued and that is
siempre ha perseguido y que es de la
communication and today being self-employed,
comunicación y a día de hoy ser autónomo
giving jobs, paying taxes should
dar trabajo el pagar impuestos debería
be proud instead of pointing the
de estar orgulloso en lugar de señalar
finger at esquel you don't
con el dedo de esquel a eso tú no la
have it flat as if it were something I know
tiene plana como si fuera algo yo sabes
with condescension as if I were stupid as if I
con condescendencia como si yo fuera
were allele no buddy
tonto como si yo fuera alelo no colega
on the contrary you who are so street you
al contrario tú que eres tan de calle
will have to say or letters eggs I don't
tendrás que decir o letras huevos no
think he will come out without resources without half
creo que salga sin recursos sin medio
look despite the hater just like me and they
mira a pesar del hater igual que yo y es
still make it worse the next one he
que todavía lo empeoran más la siguiente
goes up and if I don't lower his face
que suba el y si no le bajo la cara
[ __ ] he raps better first I am not a
ostias que rapea mejor primero yo no soy
rapper I am not freestyle it is elite
rapero yo no soy freestyle es de élite
as if it is your case that you get paid to
como si es tu caso que a ti te pagan por
go on stage and do a
subir a un escenario y hacer un
decent freestyle show I do not get paid
show de freestyle digno a mí no me pagan
to rap I am not a freestyler from the treasure I
por rapea yo no soy freestyler del teso
study downstairs mine is this mine being
estudio abajo el mío es este el mio ser
the communicator of mine is journalism  mine
el comunicador mío es periodismo el mío
on youtube mine is twitch I do my
en youtube el mío es twitch yo hago mi
job you from notebook and in the s and this I
trabajo tu de libreta y en la s y esto
lower his face [ __ ] how fast better what are you
le bajo la cara hostias que rápido mejor
looking for with that than with a
que buscas con eso que busca con una
physical threat first because you can't
amenaza física primero porque no puedes
counterargue and second this
contraargumentar y segundo esto
is simply a threat to
simplemente es una amenaza para
intimidate a journalist to
amedrentar a un periodista para que se
shut up so that another one is silenced who
calle para que se silencie otro que no
wasn't more forward shuts up I'm not
fuera más echa pa lante se calla no
going to talk about mister ego again because he's
vuelvo a hablar de míster ego porque
afraid that's it and this happens in
tiene miedo ya está y esto pasa en
politics and this happens in other sectors
política y esto pasa en otros sectores
the jump especially in politics where they try to
el salto sobre todo en política que se
silence it appears that it's
trata de buscar silenciar aparece que es
disastrous man to journalists so that they do
nefasto tío a los periodistas para que
n't say certain things
no digan según qué cosas
here there is a lot to comment on here there is a
aquí hay mucho que comentar aquí hay
lot to comment on let's go
mucho que comentar vamos a ir
break it down because it makes me laugh a lot
desgranando porque es que me hace mucha
not in addition to the personal attack
gracia no además del ataque personal
how many times have you seen mister ego
cuantas veces habéis visto míster ego
not make a professional criticism
no hacer una crítica profesionales
personal attacks chat are you going to talk to me
ataques personales chat me vas a hablar
about generating toxicity and are you going to
tú de generar toxicidad y me vas a
talk to me in ways when first you
hablar tú de formas cuando primero me
are threatening me you are talking about
estás amenazando estás hablando de
lowering my face [ __ ] for a
bajarme la cara hostias por una crítica
professional criticism and a couple of years ago I don't know
profesional y hace un par de años no sé
how much when it happened the man was
cuánto cuando ocurrió el varón estaba
looking forward to the  death male
deseando la muerte varón
barely a year ago in an
hace un año escasamente en una
interview with you for rango talking about
entrevista con ti para rango hablando de
the personal life of arcane that if it is
la vida personal de arcano que si se
repealed what is done what is stopped being done
deroga que se hace que se deja de hacer
I in your life in my life have spoken about
yo en tu vida en mi vida he hablado de
your personal life when you have
tu vida personal cuando tú si has
spoken about the rest of colleagues'
hablado del resto de compañeros de la
personal life not professional that is not
vida personal no profesional eso no es
a professional criticism you have to
una crítica profesional tienes que
differentiate between hate and insults and
diferenciar el hate y el insulto y
threats that what you are doing and
amenaza que lo que estás haciendo tú y
these are the bad ways of a
estas son las malas formas de una
professional criticism if you are freestyle the
crítica profesional si eres freestyle el
elite professional and if you want to
profesional de élite y si quiere
professionalize this the hazards of the
profesionalizar esto los gajes del
trade are the criticism of
oficio son las críticas de los
professionals one thing is that you do not
profesionales una cosa es que no
accept hate one thing that I do not accept
aceptéis el hate una cosa que no acepte
and the insults and I understand and I defend
y los insultos y lo entiendo y defiendo
that position of no to the haters no to the
esa postura de no a los haters no a los
insults but when it comes to
insultos pero cuando se trata una
professional criticism from respect
crítica profesional desde el respeto
you put up with it and you know that you have done a
te la bancás y sabes que has hecho un
bad performance you know that you have done a bad performance that's why you
mal desempeño sabes que has hecho un mal
put yourself that way the
desempeño por eso te pones de esa manera
next time you make improvements in turn it
la siguiente coges mejoras su vez te
supports you in the criticism it shuts me up
banca en la crítica me calla en la boca
with a good performance and that's it because that's what
con un buen desempeño y ya porque en eso
your work is based on there is no more and on top of that
se basa tu trabajo no hay más y encima
retweeting things like this  uncle who
retuiteando cosas de este tío que dice
really says anything about lara mister who follows you
de verdad de lara míster quien te sigue
100% for an almost logical reason
100% por una cuestión casi lógica nos
follows us this unpresentable guy really there is no
sigue este impresentable de verdad no es
need to give him more voice more voice let him do
necesario darle más voz más voz que haga
the blows and sleep and well recently we
la golpes ya dormir y bueno hace poco
were talking about everything also
estuvimos hablando de todo también
because he gave himself to me I call him a pedophile
porque él me entrego le llamo pedófilo
no no directly but well
no no directamente pero bueno
tell us if we celebrate with retweets
nos cuenta si celebramos con retweets ya
since he is generating the toxicity who in
que él está generando la toxicidad quien
total are you getting a small
total estás consiguiendo que un
group of people to persecute me in an
grupúsculo de gente me persigue de
inquisitorial manner with physical violence
manera inquisitoria con violencia física
totally the way is general
totalmente la forma es el general
toxicity and also a man like you who
toxicidad y además un hombre como tú que
says he loves the truth that is what
dice amar la verdad
bothers me the most not the
que eso es lo que más me raya no la
truth the villain character the voice of the
verdad el personaje villano la voz del
people but then when it comes down to it they
pueblo pero luego a la hora de la verdad
cannot make an agro criticism
no te pueden realizar una crítica agro
not an insult that he is not gay out there
que no un insulto que no es gay por ahí
on the secondary channel now valdano
en el canal secundario en ahora valdano
already quesada to come out he called him a pedophile
ya quesada a que salga lo llamó pedófilo
also which is a criticism and deep down
también que es una crítica y en el fondo
you know that you had a bad performance and you
sabes que tuviste un mal desempeño y ti
I want I understand how the brands
yo quiero entiendo como las marcas
because of course he works with brands
porque claro éste trabaja con marcas no
my brain lives off the brands among the
está mi cerebro vive de las marcas entre
public in  the one that I don't know how much in the in
público en el que no sé cuánto en el en
these things that I don't understand I don't know
estas cosas que yo no lo entiendo no sé
how the world of freestyle works law
cómo funciona el mundo del freestyle ley
of hands but it's the brands that
de manos pero son las marcas las que
finance that not 6 the brands
financian eso no 6 las marcas a día de
today as I took people who
hoy como cogía gente que amenazan
physically threaten you I break your face I break your
físicamente te parto la cara te reviento
mouth no what to
la boca no de qué
that how how does that fit
a eso como como cuadra eso
2 youtubers debate and fight and
2 youtubers debatan y se peleen y se
say a game well
diga un partido bueno
in a heat I can pass it we're not going to
en un calentón lo puedo pasar no vamos a
do about 3000
hacer que unos 3000
but physical aggressions at every moment or
pero agresiones físicas a cada momento o
it's like something habitual
sea como algo habitual
and to organize like here moment
y para organizar así como acá momento
well look at yourself irpa irpa is a gentleman and a
bien mirate irpa irpa es un señor y un
professional has seen to shot to go out and
profesional ha visto a tiro para salir a
say something not true because chicka is a
decir algo no verdad porque tipa es un
professional and he is a gentleman from the head to the
profesional y es un señor de la cabeza
feet he takes the criticism and the
los pies se banca la crítica y a la
next day he improves and even it's that
jornada siguiente mejora y hasta es que
we can't preach and not give wheat about
no podemos predicar y no dar trigo lo de
the toxicity the toxicity to whom is
la toxicidad la toxicidad a quien le
generating the toxicity
está generando la toxicidad
truly here in mom you tell me no
verdaderamente aquí en mamá me decís no
the way is different what he says that mister
la forma es otra lo que dice que mister
is for other things me when I say
está para otras cosas yo cuando digo
mystery he is already for other things he does
misterio ya está para otras cosas hace
more forgotten uncle by the way
más olvidada tío por cierto
but  now send the plate of the
pero ahora manda la placa del canal
secondary channel I tell you about jabil canino
secundario os digo de jabil canino
finally making way
por fin de hacer camino
I just remembered when I saw the
me acaba de acordar cuando he visto la
plate and
placa y de
the plate from which God came out is already on the
la placa del que sala dios ya está en
way the plate of Javier Canijo God
camino la placa de javier canijo dios
the first I say that he has been demanding
el primero digo que me lleva reclamando
a position on the jury for a year
un puesto en el jurado desde hace un año
since last year he has been going up and down
desde el año pasado está con vaivenes de
now yes now no now yes now no he
ahora sí ahora no ahora sí ahora no no
is not focused he does not want it does not motivate him to
está centrado no quiere no le motiva
continue in FM it is Spain the only thing that
seguir en la fm es españa lo único que
motivates him is economic capital but
le motiva es el capital económico pero
if he said it they are not my words they
si lo ha dicho él no son mis palabras
are his and it is true that nothing happens
son las suyas y es verdad que no pasa
if mister costa for other things already
nada si míster costa para otras cosas ya
not said by me or by him does not want to
no dicho por mí o por él no quiere
continue in FM it is Spain motivated him more and
seguir en fm es españa le motivaba más y
sergio meza mexico to another sad league
sergio meza méxico a otra liga triste
loyal of [ __ ] mother or to competitions that
leal de madre oa competencias que
have nothing to do with FM that yes look
no tengan que ver con fm ese sí fíjate
without going any further in redbull this
sin ir más lejos en redbull este
phenomenon as it is lost but it was
fenómeno como así perdió pero estuvo
phenomenon it does not happen that only when
fenómeno no pasa que sólo cuando se hace
a criticism is made the lover of the truth of course
una crítica el amante de la verdad claro
the one who loves the truth like mister ego
el que ama la verdad como el míster ego
only notices the criticism  then when I give
sólo se fijan las críticas luego cuando
a compliment look who generates
hago un halago fíjate quien genera
toxicity who recently calls me
toxicidad quien recientemente me llama
this pedophile I just did it a lot a
este pedófilo lo acabo de hacer mucho
couple of months ago of two edges that I
hace par de meses de dos filos que me
took advantage of the misfortunes of others
aprovechaba de las desgracias ajenas
because I made a video saying or telling
porque hice un vídeo diciendo o contando
the news that I speak not even in pieces
la noticia de que hablo ni a piezas la
had it
habían
in fact friends call him very
de hecho amigos lo llaman muy pocas
rarely to events with brands included he
veces a eventos con marcas incluidas
was lucky in 2021 but in previous
tuvo suerte el 2021 pero en anteriores
years he was only in a monthly event
años solo estaba en un evento mensual
obviously everything is due to his
obviamente todo se debe a su
behavior
comportamiento
a fight a pique a criticism and things like that
una pelea un pique una crítica y cosas
but I have seen this kid her
así pero yo lo he visto este chaval ella
several times the issue of physical threats
varias veces el tema de las amenazas
as I say that we are characters that we are
como digo que somos personajes que somos
human I
humanos
had maybe in the jungle
tuve a lo mejor en la selva que viene
a lion comes and fights with another lion to
un león y se pega con otro león para
conquer the lioness or it has just been
conquistar a la leona o recién ha sido
for food when you date but
por comida cuando citas pero personas
civilized people when in other
civilizadas cuando en otros cargos de
battery charges and
batería y
hacked the channel and that we support the
hackeado el canal y que apoyáramos la
cause to recover the channel as soon as
causa para recuperar el canal lo antes
possible thank God that is how I recover it
posible gracias a dios así lo recuperar
because I take advantage of the
porque yo me me aprovecho de las
misfortunes of others and you have campaigned
desgracias ajenas y has hecho campaña
from minute 1 to kick me off the
desde el minuto 1 para echarme de la
network and now not only those that
network y ahora no sólo esos que me
threats also what's next
amenazas también que es lo siguiente
brave it makes me laugh not about the forms
brave me hace gracia no lo de las formas
or metal this or that but if you
o metal esto o lo otro pero si
wrote vote you say nonsense much
escribiste voto tú dices burrada mucho
more beastly I do what happened to him what do you
más bestias yo hago lo que le pasó a qué
know sincerely
sabe sinceramente
what about the I
lo de la
think that I could already sue what
yo creo que ya podría demandar lo
sincerely yes quesada has never
sinceramente sí quesada nunca lo ha
said it in the serious that I think is not the
dicho en la grave que creo que no es el
case
caso
because when there is a crossing of things you
porque cuando hay un cruce de cosas
know in the end it does not get anywhere
saben al final no llega a ninguna parte
when there is a crossing of things and now what
cuando hay un cruce de cosas y ahora lo
passing the waters michu after
que de pasada las aguas michu después de
everything that winn said to him michu when there is
todo lo que le dijo winn michu cuando
a crossing of things that maybe to
hay un cruce de cosas que a lo mejor a
vitra quesada that you know is usually
vitra quesada que sabes que suele ser
more in the afternoon that is until now it
más de por la tarde que es hasta ahora
was at 3 in the morning no way if he
fue a las 3 de la mañana ni de coña si
doesn't give him a touch but come on
no le pega un toque pero vamos
basically if you want tomorrow I invite him
básicamente si queréis mañana le invito
quesada has never said when even to
quesada nunca ha dicho cuando incluso a
things that come out on other occasions he would have
cosas que sale en otras ocasiones se
heated it enjoyed it well okay
hubiera calentarla disfrutada pues vale
but [ __ ] guys that we are already talking about that
pero tíos que ya estamos hablando
knowing it defended and
de que que saberlo defendido y la
justified things that I only said a thousand
justificado cosas que yo sólo dije mil
times unjustifiable you can't
veces injustificable tú no puedes
justify that no nothing is worth it they threaten me it
justificar que no nada vale me amenazan
was like that  like the ones she told
era por el estilo como las que me dijo a
me or the ones she was going to give them, okay, the
mí o las que les iba a dar la vale
pedophiles are that the pedophiles
los de pedófilo es que los pedófilos
at that moment she would have
en ese momento a ella lo hubiera
sued her, I would have sued him
demandado yo yo lo hubiera demandado
when it happened to Quesada that he
cuando le pasó a quesada lo de que los
accused them of being a pedophile
acusó de pedófilo
and I would have sued him but they are
y lo hubiera demandado pero están siendo
traditionally being more to the face,
tradicionalmente más a la cara
ideal host, you have it done, brother, there you have it done,
ideal tienes hecho hermano allá lo
brother, you are
tienes hecho hermano
looking for arcane, I put the case of Baron
buscas arcano te pongo el caso de barón
which are personal attacks but if
que son ataques personales pero si
listen to me, you have said something about go to
escúchame que has dicho algo de vete a
very similar
muy parecido
that they have made me lower the stinking
que me han hecho bajarle apestoso la
torch starting from the base starting
antorcha partiendo de la base partiendo
from the base that you make a stinking box
de la base de que haces una casilla
for your companions, look, you are going to
para los compañeros fíjate me vas a
talk to me in the form of
hablar tú de forma
suppliers, forms of the entire dinner and that you
proveedores formas de toda la cena y que
buy the character and allow him
le compras el personaje y le permitir
any insult, any lack of
cualquier insulto cualquier falta de
respect because Mr. ego
respeto porque el míster ego
because Mr. ego, look if someone
porque el míster ego fíjate si lo
else did it then general toxicity,
hiciera otro luego general toxicidad
talk about forms but to tell us that
hablar de formas pero que decirnos que
where you fail, where you fail, where you fail, you
donde fallas donde fallas donde fallas
write mystery is for other things,
escribe misterio está para otras cosas
the truth then, well, there it
la verdad entonces bueno pues ahí se
stays, I love him  a lot to poncho but he
queda yo le quiero mucho a poncho pero
is very good as a caster or he is very good
está muy bien de caster o está muy bien
as a caster I love him very much but he is
de caster yo le quiero mucho pero está
very good as a caster because for crystals he is
muy bien de caster porque para cristales
no longer ok respectable and I even
ya no está ok respetables y yo incluso
also think that go to I did not see him no he
también pienso que vete a no le vi no él
would do well in a competition like fms
le venía bien una competición como fms
for real because we did not have a
de verdad porque no teníamos un
structured character because it gave him
personaje estructurado porque le daba
a lot of anxiety because on a personal level I think
mucha ansiedad porque a nivel personal
that no no it did not contribute that much but it
creo que no no no le aportaba tanto pero
is the same case it is the same case you
es el mismo caso es el mismo caso tú
can say it and make a criticism of
puedes decirlo y hacer una crítica a
another colleague but I am not a lover of the
otro compañero pero yo no amante de la
truth for when it interests us I stay
verdad para cuando nos interesa me quedo
with him with the issue of pay per view
con él con el tema del pago por visión
not recently we talked about it no no it is that
no recientemente lo hablábamos no no es
I professionalize this we have to
que yo profesionalizar esto tenemos que
charge more because the pay per view
cobrar más por que el pago por visión
because this for the other if you want the
porque esto por lo otro si queréis los
benefits
beneficios
of professionalism but you do not want the
de la profesionalidad pero no queréis la
other side of the coin keep in mind what
otra cara de la moneda tened en cuenta
day it seems to me that he knows how to
lo que el día me parece que sabe
give me a [ __ ] sweatshirt that explodes
regalarme una sudadera de estallar
in a nice color is to know what I am going to
en un color guapo es saber qué
throw at it the clothes
voy a echarla la ropa
what you have to do give me one
lo que tienes que hacer regalarme una
of these clothes
una ropita de ésta
now the clothes are there
ahora está la ropa
everyone sends me things so I do not
todo el mundo me mandan cosas así que no
know what you expect  host see there is the duck I
sé qué esperas ve está el pato me
like in gray in cracks of the duck I
gusta en gris en grietas del pato me
like in gray or is this city was I
gusta en gris o está esta ciudad era me
like quesada is like this in blue look how
gusta quesada es así en azul mire qué
pretty
guapa
send me something and I'll wear it I
mándame algo y me lo pongo
pay for sure they don't send it to me and I
pago seguro no me lo mandan y me los
'll wear it said look at the store to quesada tomorrow that tickets are paid that tickets are paid they already pay a salary so that you put on worthy shows they already pay you so that you go home the critics evidently I understand I have seen absolutely nothing wrong with that click on speakers you already want to
en ese clic en ponentes ya queréis
charge more you want the benefits of
cobrar más queréis los beneficios de los
professionals but you don't want the other
profesionales pero no queréis la otra
side of the coin which are the hazards of the
cara de la moneda que son los gajes del
trade because I am totally
oficio porque yo estoy totalmente
convinced and I removed this I am
convencido y esto lo quité estoy
totally convinced in any other
totalmente convencido en cualquier otra
professional discipline without
disciplina profesional sin competidor de
elite competitor threatens any journalist
élite amenaza a cualquier periodista
at least they give you a touch a
mínimo le dan un toque una sanción
financial sanction or a suspension
económica o una suspensión
heavy
pesado
here while they ask you for pay per view
aquí mientras te piden pago por visión
to charge what is fair what I
para cobrar el que es justo lo que
feel in other words
siento ósea
a topic that is about brand these people the
un tema que va de marca esta gente los
freestylers live off the brands they do not
freestylers viven de las marcas no lo
hire them in the events of the events
contratan en los eventos de los eventos
the brands organize them not
los organizan las marcas no
as the brands continue calling those
como las marcas siguen llamando esas
souls and continue in a media bubble
almas y seguir en una burbuja mediática
because it is not the first time
porque no es la primera vez no ocurre
nothing happens here nothing happens here we want
nada aquí no ocurre nada aquí queremos
pay per view to charge more but then when it comes
pago por visión cobrar más pero luego a
down to it imagine
la hora de la verdad tú imagínate
brother that suddenly a soccer player,
hermano que de repente un futbolista un
I who know anything a tennis player whatever whatever
yo que se cualquier cosa un tenista lo
another professional from any other
otro profesional de cualquier otra
discipline threatens a journalist for
disciplina amenaza a un periodista por
giving his opinion that we are not talking
dar su opinión que no estamos hablando
a personal attack remember it is a
un ataque personal recordad es una
professional criticism at all times
crítica profesional en todo momento
I want that to be clear imagine
quiero que quede eso claro tú imagínate
my brother that a soccer player takes a call
mi hermano que un futbolista coge llame
30 and threatens to silence that
30 y amenaza para silenciar a ese
journalist totally auguro in that
periodista totalmente agüero de esa
way he is given a financial sanction he is
manera se le mete una sanción económica
suspended from work and minimum wage for
se le suspende de empleo y sueldo mínimo
a month this type
un mes no se pueden permitir este tipo
of things cannot be allowed with the glass or do we normalize
de cosas con el cristal o normalizamos
it, I don't know if it's because of the belligerence
tiene yo no sé si es por la beligerancia
of the cold the hostility that exists within
del frío la hostilidad que hay dentro
freestyle because in the end this goes
del freestyle porque al final esto se
down we are actions well insults and cough
baja somos acciones bien insultos y tos
but it's something that I don't understand then it's not
pero es algo que no comprendo luego no
that we have to separate the character from
es que hay que separar el personaje de
the person what is clear is that what is
la persona lo que queda claro que se
said on stage is part of the show
dice en la tarima lo que es del show se
stays there and then these things happen and
queda ahí y luego pasan estas cosas y
because they are not characters that come out and in the
porque no son personajes que salgan y al
end it is someone and they will tell me I was right
final es alguien y me dirá tenía razón
as the tweet has put it, it is not a
como bien ha puesto el tuit no es un
character and I told them that someone
personaje y se lo dije que sale alguien
who came comes out is not a character, to me those
que vino no es un personaje a mí esas
things and that and that fanaticism, well no, well
cosas y eso y esa hinchada pues no pues
no, you can be a bit of a character, I
no tú puedes hacer un poco personaje yo
really am
en verdad
something more the [ __ ] of the account
algo más el de la cuenta
when they had the internet, well yes, of course, yes, I am
cuando tenían internet pues sí claro
a character, not the
pues sí soy un personaje no las
opinions works, I invent
opiniones obras invento
that I exaggerate a little and I make a little more
que exagere un poco y hago un poco más
of an electoral gesture and I am a little
de gesto electoralización y soy un poco
more this era here okay
más esta era aquí vale
but to her that from there to being a
pero a ella que de ahí a que sea un
character,
personaje
people encouraging us to be missionaries
gente alentando a que seamos misioneros
and part of the face
y parte de la cara
wow very worrying because I
wow muy preocupante porque yo
truly during all these months
verdaderamente durante todos estos meses
if I could give you a
si te podía hacer una crítica
professional criticism, she has done it to you just as I
profesional te la ha hecho al igual que
could wash your echo cuenca oslo, I
te podía lavarte la echo cuenca oslo
work a character jagger, I don't know
trabajo un personaje jagger no lo sé
because I don't see it but the characters, I did not
porque no lo veo pero los personajes no
say that it is only a character,
dije que sólo es un personaje
characters, visa mastercard period but
personajes el visa mastercard punto pero
like that, visa mastercard
así el visa mastercard
adelita power, those two characters
adelita power esos dos personajes
changes only only sun has been to
cambios solo solo sol ha sido a
destroy me only that yes, pedophile that if
destruirme solo que sí pedófilo que si
I took advantage of the misfortunes  foreign that
me aproveche las desgracias ajenas que
outside the network that can not
fuera de la network que no pueda
react to my battles that will not be
reaccionar a mis batallas que no serán
okay now the last thing that can come
está bien ya lo último que puede llegar
to this is let's go that you are 30 years old
es a esto vamos que tienes 30 años
brother that you are a lover of the truth
brother que eres amante de la verdad
according to what you say bank you what I am not
según dices banca te lo que no te estoy
facing you respect that I am not
afrontando respeto que no te estoy
enjoying you that no hate is a
disfrutando que no hate es una crítica
professional criticism pau len paul's character
profesional pau león personaje de paul
is a lamentable character paula was going to
es un personaje lamentable paula iba a
be a [ __ ] video ok
ser vídeo ok
paula very strong god
paula muy fuerte dios
every time there is something in which he can
cada vez que hay algo en lo que puede
charge he gets out of the way
cobrar se quita de en medio
say good food
decir buena comida
every time he has the opportunity of
cada vez que tiene la oportunidad de
something that he can charge
algo que puede cobrar
if I have to edit it today I have no
si lo tengo que editar hoy no tengo
homework
tarea
da da disgusting da disgusting da
da da asco
next day you train you improve
a la siguiente jornada entrenas mejoras
you get on stage
te subes al escenario
and you are a professional who pays you for something which is that
y eres profesional que para algo te paga
you also boast of
que es que además tú mismo te jactas de
not training so what do you expect from the
no entrenar entonces qué esperas del
performance that you want in an
rendimiento que desee en una competencia
elite competition I say I achieved a position as a
de élite yo digo lograba puesto por
joke I have to have the same
guasa tengo que tener la misma vara de
measuring stick for everyone so that's what there is
medir para todo el mundo así que eso es
for me to shut up silence me
lo que hay a mí callar me silenciarme
with threats of course not and  look
con amenazas desde luego que no y fíjate
how easy it is for me since six
que lo tengo muy fácil desde hace seis
months ago I could have filed a complaint
meses podría haber te metió una querella
against you, [ __ ] it from the moment you
ya tomar por culo desde el momento que
call me a pedophile, [ __ ] it
me llamas pedófilos a tomar por culo
lucky that I'm not involved yet I
suerte que todavía no está metido de
really pass the need to get into
verdad paso necesidad de meterme en
lawsuits
pleitos
that didn't happen man there is the issue of this
eso no lo pasó tío está el tema de este
judicial system and I
sistema judicial y
understand that another piece of solution that's why
entiendo que otra pieza de solución por
when we were in the debate with
eso cuando estuvimos en el debate con
javi oliveira that I defended you and spread
javi oliveira que te defendí y difundir
freestyle I
freestyle
already have to carved oh god
ya tengo que talló ay dios
it's true in fact I'm
es cierto de hecho ya estoy hasta los
fed up with this this is really difficult that there is
huevos de esto esto está el huevo de que
a fight a controversy and you go out to
haya una pelea una polémica y salgas a
live you
vivir a ti
I'm fed up with this I
estoy hasta los huevos de esto
'm fed up with it I don't see it
estoy hasta los huevos no lo veo
necessary but say that this position for
necesario pero di que este puesto para
a slogan posted on whatsapp that I
un lema puesto en el whatsapp que yo le
do on the skin imagine telling your
haga en la piel imagínate decirle a tu
boss or rather imagine telling your boss
jefe o sea imagínate decirle a tu jefe
imagine me telling you paulo there is work
imagínate que te digo paulo hay trabajo
today
hoy
no I don't have anyone because I exist I don't know
no no tengo a nadie porque existo no sé
what and the other 11 when I have no one to
qué y el otro 11 cuando no tengo a nadie
take the video of tomorrow's principal
que me saque el vídeo del principal de
paulo there is work you can charge
mañana paulo hay trabajo puedes cobrar
maybe  paulo
alomejor paulo
imagine telling your boss I have
imagínate decirle a tu jefe
homework we can exchange don't
tengo tarea hacemos un intercambio no te
complain you do my homework and I'll
quejes tú me haces la tarea y yo te
edit the video
editó el vídeo
imagine telling everyone he says okay look
imagínate decirles a todo dice vale mira
javi you do my homework and I'll make
javi tú me haces la tarea y yo te hago
the video
el vídeo
no
no
imagine your boss sends you something he
imagínate que tu jefe te manda algo
unloads this truck that's working an hour of
descarga este camión que hace una hora
overtime and you tell him
extra y tú le dices
my mother sent me for your fruit
mi madre me mandó por las frutas de tú
for my mother's fruit
por las frutas de mi madre
imagine man how this is going well I ca
imagínate tío cómo avanza esto ahí pues
n't stand it
no aguanto
because out of pity for pity because I got it
porque por pena por pena porque lo cogí
from twitter I felt sorry for
de de twitter me dio lástima
jeans or I was
vaqueros o
trying to get
trataba de que ya que estabais hablando
you to forget the differences without
nos olvidéis las diferencias sin
having to go to court that they are
necesidad de ir a un juzgado que son
some messes so that to earn
unos embrollos lo para que para ganar
half five thousand euros at your expense 5,000
medio cinco mil euros a tu costa 5.000
10,000 he bought me a car if he wants for
10.000 me compró un coche si quiere para
that 5,000 10,000 I walk it around the
con esos 5.000 10.000 lo paseo por el
neighborhood I say look thanks mystery I don't
barrio digo mira gracias misterio no
have the need he loves me it bores me that
tengo la necesidad me ama me aburre eso
but I press month and day half I
pero pulso mes y el día media me
find the needs well look for
encuentro las necesidades pues mira por
threats
amenazas
[Music]
[Música]
a person to
una persona
approach him well that is an option you
abordarlo bueno esa es una opción que lo
know it is not a threat I
sepas no es una amenaza simplemente te
'm simply telling you what there is the threat of
estoy diciendo lo que hay la amenaza del
stalking you one thing is to say mister ego
asecho tú una cosa es decir míster ego
you are [ __ ] you are not worth this this the
eres un no vales para esto esto
other is a lie that because mister ego
el otro es mentira eso porque mister ego
is an elite freestyler who has been
es un freestyler de élite que lleva aquí
rapping here at stratospheric levels at the
rapeando a niveles estratosféricos al
top level for years and has a lot of
nivel top desde hace años y tiene mucha
value but well well it's like him like to
valía pero ya pues bueno es como el como
tell you like the 36 37 38
decirte como el futbolista de 36 37 38
year old soccer player who is still here has about two
años que aún sigue le quedan unas dos
more seasons left and because Maldini has taken over he
temporadas más y porque ha cogido
told him well man you had
maldini le ha dicho pues tío has hecho
a bad game
un mal partido
well
bueno
in total
en total
he is right
tenga razón
thanks to whoever sympathizes with that
gracias a aquel que simpatiza con el
idiot to stop following me or
idiota ese que me deje de seguir o se
demonstrate here that I already blocked him I am a
manifieste aquí que ya le bloqueo yo
nightmare you are and the one who Monetti
pesadilla soy vosotros y el que monetti
knows what he wants and if you like the salsa singer
se lo que quiera y si os mola el salsero
telling him to leave the house it makes me laugh
decirle que salga de casa me hace gracia
that you continue with your thirteen man do not sell
que sigas en tus trece macho no vendan
the movie that I do not leave the house because I am
la película que no salgo de casa porque
afraid to go out on the street because I
tengo miedo a salir a la calle que yo
go out every day to buy bread  and
salgo todos los días a comprar el pan y
every party weekend I also remind you
todos los findes de fiesta te recuerdo
that we were in the same hotel
además que estuvimos en el mismo hotel
in Madrid
en madrid
and
e
Girona and thank you very much thank you
gerona y muchas gracias muchas gracias
for heroes successes
por héroes éxitos
but it is success
pero es éxito
thank you
gracias
but it is success friend I will not have
pero es amigo de éxito no voy a tener
casinos directors has apparently done
casinos directivos ha hecho por lo visto
a live
un directo
and we have but now
y tenemos pero ya
because I am leaving family because I am
porque ya me voy familiar porque ya me
leaving family well what I said listen to me what I
voy familia bueno lo dicho escúchame
said
lo dicho
great today of salt 03 hours
buenísimo el día de hoy de sal 03 horas
three hours or kids with you but
tres horas o chavalería con ustedes pero
well what I said family from now on
bueno lo dicho familia a partir de ahora
Javier Kan ism is going to work the same as
javier kan ismo va a funcionar igual que
Tevez to the CEO news
tevez al ceo noticia
live the live shows remain in their entirety
directos los directos se quedan enteros
summarized the live shows are first in
resumidos los directos son primero en
tweets and the next day they are
tweets y al día siguiente
broadcast again in
se vuelve a emitir en
extracts
extractos
and the best videos and the best
y los mejores videos y el mejor
content is the canijo the quality content
contenido es el canijo el contenido de
tomorrow there will be no video because I don't have an
mañana no hay vídeo porque no tengo
editor
editor
three hours and I have a new friend
tres horas y tengo un nuevo amigo
the live shows remain in the canijo
los directos se quedan en el canijo
public yes but there is another video quesada
público sí pero hay otro vídeo quesada
well tomorrow tomorrow
pues ya mañana mañana
when I am going to bed family see you
que me voy a la cama familia nos vemos
tomorrow a hug
mañana un abrazo
[Music]
[Música]